<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to The libptpmgmt Project on libptpmgmt Project</title><link>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to The libptpmgmt Project on libptpmgmt Project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>401 - Unauthorized Access</title><link>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/401/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/401/</guid><description>This page requires a login as an authorized user.</description></item><item><title>403 - Forbidden</title><link>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/403/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/403/</guid><description>You do not have permission to view this page.</description></item><item><title>404 - Page Not Found</title><link>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/404/</guid><description>Oops! We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find that page.
Please check the URL or try searching for related content using the search box at the top of this page.</description></item><item><title>500 - Internal Server Error</title><link>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/500/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/500/</guid><description>The web server encountered an error that prevented it from loading this page. Please try again later.
If the issue persists, you can report the error to webmaster.</description></item><item><title>libptpmgmt Library to Communicate with IEEE 1558 PTP Clocks</title><link>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/documentation/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://libptpmgmt.nwtime.org/documentation/readme/</guid><description>libptpmgmt Library to Communicate with IEEE 1558 PTP Clocks Preface The library for PTP management client uses IEEE 1558 management messages to communicate with PTP entities over the network. We support get, set and command of all management TLVs that are described in IEEE 1588-2019. In addition, we support LinuxPTP specific implementation management TLVs.
The library supports the three PTP network layers:
UDP over IP version 4 UDP over IP version 6 PTP over Ethernet — we do not support VLAN tags In addition, we support using the Unix network and communicate with LinuxPTP ptp4l.</description></item></channel></rss>